citehr.com 2018-10-04

# Privacy Policy - CiteMan Network

We recognize that your privacy is very important and take it seriously. Our CiteMan Network Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes our policies and procedures on the collection, use, disclosure, and sharing of your information when you use the Cite.Co Platform. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to activities by CiteMan Network and its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively “CiteMan Network,” “we” or “us”) .

**The Information We Collect**

We collect information directly from individuals, from third-parties and automatically through the CiteMan Network Platform.

**_Account and Profile Information_** : When you create an account and profile on the CiteMan Network Platform, we collect your name, contact information, and other information you provide, such as topics that you know about or find interesting. Your name, photo, and any other information that you choose to add to your public-facing profile will be available for viewing to users of the CiteMan Network Platform. Once you activate a profile, other users will be able to see in your profile certain information about your activity on the CiteMan Network Platform, such as the questions and answers you post, your followers and who you follow, topics of interest to you, the information you list as credentials, and your edits to Your Content. 

**_Communications_**. When you communicate with us (via email, phone, through the CiteMan Network Platform or otherwise), we may maintain a record of your communication.

**_Integrated Service Provider and Linked Networks.Â  _**If you elect to connect your CiteMan Network account to another online service provider, such as a social networking service (“Integrated Service Provider”), you will be allowing us to pass to and receive from the Integrated Service Provider your log-in information and other user data. You may elect to sign in or sign up to the CiteMan Network Platform through a linked network like Facebook or Google (each a “Linked Network”). If you elect to sign up through a Linked Network, you will be asked to enable sharing of your contacts with CiteMan Network. If you agree to this sharing, in order to facilitate a more connected experience, we may send notices informing your contacts you have joined CiteMan Network so that you and your contacts can find and follow each other on the CiteMan Network Platform. The specific information we may collect varies by Integrated Service Provider, but the permissions page for each will describe the relevant information. Integrated Service Providers control how they use and share your information; you should consult their respective privacy policies for information about their practices.

**_Automatically Collected Information About Your Activity_**. We use cookies, log files and other tracking technologies to automatically collect information about your activities, such as your searches, page views, date and time of your visit, and other information about your use of the CiteMan Network Platform. We also collect and may store information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the CiteMan Network Platform such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, location, and requested and referring URLs. ****We also receive information when you view content on or otherwise interact with the CiteMan Network Platform, even if you have not created an account. For more information, see the Cookies, Pixels and Tracking section below.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites. 
  * Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)   

**How We Share Your Information**

We share information as set forth below, and where individuals have otherwise consented:

**_Service Providers._** We may share your information with third party service providers who use this information to perform services for us, such as payment processors, hosting providers, auditors, advisors, consultants, customer service and support providerss.

**_Affiliates_** _.Â  _The information collected about you may be accessed by or shared with subsidiaries and affiliates of CiteMan Network, whose use and disclosure of your personal information is subject to this Privacy Policy.

**_Business Transfers.Â  _**We may disclose or transfer information, including personal data, as part of any merger, sale, and transfer of our assets, acquisition or restructuring of all or part of our business, bankruptcy, or similar event.

**_Legally Required.Â  _**We may disclose your information if we are required to do so by law.

**_Protection of Rights.Â  _**We may disclose information where we believe it necessary to respond to claims asserted against us or, comply with legal process (e.g., subpoenas or warrants), enforce or administer our agreements and terms, for fraud prevention, risk assessment, investigation, and protect the rights, property or safety of CiteMan Network, its users, or others.

**_Your Content and Activity.Â  _**Your Content, including your name, profile picture, profile information, and certain associated activity information is available to other users of the CiteMan Network Platform and may be viewed publicly. Public viewing includes availability to non-registered visitors and can occur when users share Your Content across other sites or services. In addition, Your Content may be indexed by search engines. See the section below about Your Choices for information about how you may change how certain information is shared or viewed by others.

**_Ad Metrics.Â  _**We may share with users of our Ad Services aggregate statistics, metrics and other reports about the performance of their ads or content in the CiteMan Network Platform such as the number of unique user views, demographics about the users who saw their ads or content, conversion rates, and date and time information. We do not share IP addresses or personal information. We may also allow our advertisers to use Pixels on the CiteMan Network Platform in order to collect information about the performance of their ads.

**_Anonymized and Aggregated Data._** Â We may share aggregate or de-identified information with third parties for research, marketing, analytics and other purposes, provided such information does not identify a particular individual.

**Cookies, Pixels and Tracking**

We and our third party providers use cookies, clear GIFs/pixel tags, JavaScript, local storage, log files, and other mechanisms to automatically collect and record information about your usage and browsing activities on the CiteMan Network Platform and across third party sites or online services. We may combine this information with other information we collect about users. Below, we provide a brief summary these activities.

  * _Cookies.Â  _These are small files with a unique identifier that are transferred to your browser through our websites. They allow us to remember users who are logged in, to understand how users navigate through and use the CiteMan Network Platform, and to display personalized content and targeted ads (including on third party sites and applications).
  * _Analytics Tools.Â  _We may use internal and third party analytics tools, includingÂ [ _Google Analytics_](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en). The third party analytics companies we work with may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online products and services. Their collection and use of information is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Do-Not-Track Signals.Â  **Please note we do not change system behavior within the CiteMan Network Platform in response to browser requests not to be tracked.

**How We Protect Your Information**

The security of your information is important to us. CiteMan Network has implemented safeguards to protect the information we collect. However, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal data safe, such as choosing strong password and keeping it private, as well as logging out of your user account, and closing your web browser when finished using the CiteMan Network Platform.

**Access and Amend Your Information**

You may update or correct your account information at any time by logging in to your account. You may also make a number of other adjustments to settings or the display of information about you as described in more detail in the following section about Your Choices.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

The CiteMan Network Platform may contain links to third party sites or online services. We are not responsible for the practices of such third parties, whose information practices are subject to their own policies and procedures, not to this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially change how we treat your personal information, we will endeavor to provide you with reasonable notice of such changes, such as via prominent notice in the CiteMan Network Platform or to your email address of record, and where required by law, we will obtain your consent or give you the opportunity to opt out of such changes.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions about our practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us atÂ [ _support@cite.co_](mailto:support@cite.co), or send mail to:

CiteMan Network  
BC 23, Nirvana Country, Sector 50, Gurugram, Haryana - 122018
